<resources>
  <string name="app_name">Jarvis</string>
  <string name="accessibility_service_description">Jarvis Assistant requires accessibility access to provide system-wide assistance, overlay controls, and intelligent automation features.</string>

  <!-- Permission Rationale Strings -->
  <string name="permission_rationale_record_audio">Jarvis needs microphone access to understand your voice commands and have conversations with you.</string>
  <string name="permission_rationale_camera">Camera access allows Jarvis to help with visual tasks like scanning documents and recognizing objects.</string>
  <string name="permission_rationale_post_notifications">Notification permission lets Jarvis send you important alerts and reminders.</string>
  <string name="permission_rationale_sms">SMS access allows Jarvis to help manage your text messages and send messages on your behalf.</string>
  <string name="permission_rationale_contacts">Contact access helps Jarvis understand who you\'re talking about and manage your address book.</string>
  <string name="permission_rationale_read_phone_state">Phone state access helps Jarvis understand when you\'re in a call and provide appropriate assistance.</string>
  <string name="permission_rationale_system_alert_window">Overlay permission allows Jarvis to show helpful information and controls on top of other apps.</string>
  <string name="permission_rationale_write_settings">Settings access lets Jarvis adjust system settings for automation and convenience.</string>
  <string name="permission_rationale_notification_listener">Notification access allows Jarvis to read and manage all your notifications intelligently.</string>
  <string name="permission_rationale_accessibility_service">Accessibility service enables Jarvis to provide system-wide assistance and automation.</string>
  <string name="permission_rationale_query_all_packages">Package visibility helps Jarvis understand what apps you have installed for better integration.</string>

  <!-- TickTick Integration -->
  <string name="ticktick_channel_name">TickTick</string>
  <string name="ticktick_channel_description">Persistent notifications for TickTick tasks</string>
  <string name="ticktick_tasks">Tasks</string>
  <string name="ticktick_loading">Loading</string>
  <string name="ticktick_no_tasks">No tasks to display</string>
  <string name="ticktick_today">Today</string>
  <string name="ticktick_overdue">OVERDUE</string>
  <string name="ticktick_upcoming">UPCOMING</string>
  <string name="ticktick_add_task">Add task</string>
  <string name="ticktick_refresh">Refresh</string>
  <string name="permission_rationale_ticktick">TickTick task access allows Jarvis to display your tasks and provide task management.</string>

  <!-- Permission UI Strings -->
  <string name="permission_open_app_settings">Open App Settings</string>
</resources>
